{
  "chapters": [
    {
      "chapter_number": 1,
      "multiple_choice": [
        {
          "number": 1,
          "question": "Jem broke his arm badly at the elbow when he was nearly how old, according to the narrator in Chapter 1?",
          "options": [
            "10",
            "12",
            "13",
            "8"
          ],
          "answer": "13"
        },
        {
          "number": 2,
          "question": "How many years older is Jem than his sister Scout?",
          "options": [
            "1 year older",
            "4 years older",
            "2 years older",
            "3 years older"
          ],
          "answer": "4 years older"
        },
        {
          "number": 3,
          "question": "In Chapter 1, the narrator says, \"Being Southerners, it was a source of shame to some members of the family that we had no recorded ancestors on either side of\" what battle?",
          "options": [
            "The Battle of Hastings",
            "The Battle of Fontenoy",
            "The Battle of Shiloh",
            "The Battle of Austerlitz"
          ],
          "answer": "The Battle of Hastings"
        },
        {
          "number": 4,
          "question": "Simon Finch is described in Chapter 1 as a fur-trapping apothecary from what location?",
          "options": [
            "Paris",
            "Jordan",
            "Cornwall",
            "Maine"
          ],
          "answer": "Cornwall"
        },
        {
          "number": 5,
          "question": "What is the name of the homestead that Simon Finch established for himself in Alabama?",
          "options": [
            "The Finch's Nest",
            "Finch's Orchard and Estates",
            "Finch's Landing",
            "The Finch Perch"
          ],
          "answer": "Finch's Landing"
        },
        {
          "number": 6,
          "question": "According to the narrator in Chapter 1, where did Atticus Finch go to study law?",
          "options": [
            "New York, New York",
            "Mobile, Alabama",
            "Boston, Massachusetts",
            "Hartford, Connecticut"
          ],
          "answer": "Mobile, Alabama"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "chapter_number": 2,
      "multiple_choice": [
        {
          "number": 7,
          "question": "Where does Dill live during the school year?",
          "options": [
            "Montague, California",
            "Meridian, Mississippi",
            "Malvern, Arkansas",
            "Clinton, Texas"
          ],
          "answer": "Meridian, Mississippi"
        },
        {
          "number": 8,
          "question": "What grade in school is Scout starting in Chapter 2?",
          "options": [
            "Fourth grade",
            "First grade",
            "Third grade",
            "Second grade"
          ],
          "answer": "First grade"
        },
        {
          "number": 9,
          "question": "What grade is Jem starting school in Chapter 2?",
          "options": [
            "Fourth grade",
            "Sixth grade",
            "Fifth grade",
            "Third grade"
          ],
          "answer": "Fifth grade"
        },
        {
          "number": 10,
          "question": "What is the name of Scout's schoolteacher in Chapter 2?",
          "options": [
            "Miss Julie Anderson",
            "Miss Sarah Roberts",
            "Miss Caroline Fisher",
            "Miss Cathy Smith"
          ],
          "answer": "Miss Caroline Fisher"
        },
        {
          "number": 11,
          "question": "What county in Alabama does Scout's schoolteacher say she's from in Chapter 2?",
          "options": [
            "Jefferson County",
            "Pike County",
            "Birmingham County",
            "Winston County"
          ],
          "answer": "Winston County"
        },
        {
          "number": 12,
          "question": "On what date did Alabama secede from the Union during the Civil War era?",
          "options": [
            "March 1, 1860",
            "September 14, 1862",
            "July 12, 1860",
            "January 11, 1861"
          ],
          "answer": "January 11, 1861"
        },
        {
          "number": 13,
          "question": "How much money does Scout's teacher offer to loan to the little boy who has no lunch with him in Chapter 2?",
          "options": [
            "2 dollars",
            "10 cents",
            "25 cents",
            "1 dollar"
          ],
          "answer": "25 cents"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "chapter_number": 3,
      "multiple_choice": [
        {
          "number": 14,
          "question": "What is the name of the little boy that has no lunch with him at school in Chapter 2?",
          "options": [
            "Walter Cunningham",
            "Peter Dawkins",
            "Jesse Thomas",
            "Jamie Smith"
          ],
          "answer": "Walter Cunningham"
        },
        {
          "number": 15,
          "question": "What does Walter Cunningham pour all over his food that causes Scout to exclaim in Chapter 3?",
          "options": [
            "Gravy",
            "Molasses",
            "Honey",
            "Milk"
          ],
          "answer": "Molasses"
        },
        {
          "number": 16,
          "question": "Who invites Walter Cunningham to come to the Finch home for dinner in Chapter 3?",
          "options": [
            "Calpurnia",
            "Scout",
            "Jem",
            "Atticus"
          ],
          "answer": "Jem"
        },
        {
          "number": 17,
          "question": "How does Scout say Calpurnia's grammar changes whenever she is furious in Chapter 3?",
          "options": [
            "It becomes nonsensical",
            "It becomes heightened",
            "It becomes precise",
            "It becomes erratic"
          ],
          "answer": "It becomes erratic"
        },
        {
          "number": 18,
          "question": "Where does Calpurnia make Scout eat the rest of her dinner after she's insulted Walter in Chapter 3?",
          "options": [
            "In the living room",
            "In the library",
            "In the kitchen",
            "In her bedroom"
          ],
          "answer": "In the kitchen"
        },
        {
          "number": 19,
          "question": "Where does Scout threaten to go and drown herself in Chapter 3?",
          "options": [
            "The Atlantic Ocean",
            "The Pacific Ocean",
            "Barker's Eddy",
            "The Mississippi River"
          ],
          "answer": "Barker's Eddy"
        },
        {
          "number": 20,
          "question": "Who is the little boy that Scout's teacher sees a \"cootie\" crawling on in Chapter 3?",
          "options": [
            "Burris Ewell",
            "Maxwell Green",
            "Heck Tate",
            "Link Deas"
          ],
          "answer": "Burris Ewell"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "chapter_number": 4,
      "multiple_choice": [
        {
          "number": 21,
          "question": "What does Atticus say the Ewell family patriarch spends his relief checks on in Chapter 3?",
          "options": [
            "Prostitutes",
            "Horse races",
            "Whiskey",
            "Lawyers"
          ],
          "answer": "Whiskey"
        },
        {
          "number": 22,
          "question": "At what time does Scout get out of school each day in Chapter 4?",
          "options": [
            "3:30 p.m",
            "2:30 p.m",
            "2:00 p.m",
            "3:00 p.m"
          ],
          "answer": "2:30 p.m"
        },
        {
          "number": 23,
          "question": "What does Scout find in the knothole of the oak tree at the Radley Place in the beginning of Chapter 4?",
          "options": [
            "Chewing gum",
            "Soap figurines",
            "A ball of twine",
            "Wooden chess pieces"
          ],
          "answer": "Chewing gum"
        },
        {
          "number": 24,
          "question": "What items are contained in the jewelry box that Scout and Jem find in the knothole in Chapter 4?",
          "options": [
            "Wooden figurines",
            "Potatoes",
            "Indian-head pennies",
            "Chess pieces"
          ],
          "answer": "Indian-head pennies"
        },
        {
          "number": 25,
          "question": "Who lives at the far end of Scout's street next door to the post office in Chapter 4?",
          "options": [
            "Link Deas",
            "Tensaw Jones",
            "Cecil Jacobs",
            "Maxwell Green"
          ],
          "answer": "Cecil Jacobs"
        },
        {
          "number": 26,
          "question": "Who is described in Chapter 4 as \"the meanest old woman who ever lived\"?",
          "options": [
            "Mrs. Dubose",
            "Miss Emily Davis",
            "Calpurnia",
            "Miss Maudie"
          ],
          "answer": "Mrs. Dubose"
        },
        {
          "number": 27,
          "question": "Scout says in Chapter 4 that the train stop called Maycomb Junction is actually in what county?",
          "options": [
            "Montgomery County",
            "Warren County",
            "Lafayette County",
            "Abbott County"
          ],
          "answer": "Abbott County"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "chapter_number": 5,
      "multiple_choice": [
        {
          "number": 28,
          "question": "Who picks up Dill at the train station in Maycomb's one taxi in Chapter 4?",
          "options": [
            "Scout",
            "Atticus Finch",
            "Miss Rachel",
            "Jem"
          ],
          "answer": "Miss Rachel"
        },
        {
          "number": 29,
          "question": "What does Miss Maudie detest growing in her yard?",
          "options": [
            "Nut grass",
            "Crab grass",
            "Dandelions",
            "Tulips"
          ],
          "answer": "Nut grass"
        },
        {
          "number": 30,
          "question": "What is Dill's real name?",
          "options": [
            "Charles Baker Harris",
            "Truman Harris",
            "Jack Harris",
            "William Peter Harris"
          ],
          "answer": "Charles Baker Harris"
        },
        {
          "number": 31,
          "question": "What does Miss Maudie say Boo Radley's name is in Chapter 5?",
          "options": [
            "Arthur",
            "Boris",
            "Brett",
            "James"
          ],
          "answer": "Arthur"
        },
        {
          "number": 32,
          "question": "What is the name of Atticus Finch's brother?",
          "options": [
            "Edward Finch",
            "Jack Finch",
            "George Finch",
            "William Finch"
          ],
          "answer": "Jack Finch"
        },
        {
          "number": 33,
          "question": "What was the name of Miss Maudie's father?",
          "options": [
            "Dr. Frank Buford",
            "Mr. Tensaw Jones",
            "Mr. Link Deas",
            "Maxwell Green"
          ],
          "answer": "Dr. Frank Buford"
        },
        {
          "number": 34,
          "question": "What household pets does Jem suggest Boo Radley eats in Chapter 5?",
          "options": [
            "Parakeets",
            "Goldfish",
            "Cats",
            "Dogs"
          ],
          "answer": "Cats"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "chapter_number": 6,
      "multiple_choice": [
        {
          "number": 35,
          "question": "What does Jem use to try to deliver a message to Boo Radley in Chapter 5?",
          "options": [
            "A slingshot",
            "A paper airplane",
            "A fishing pole",
            "A rock"
          ],
          "answer": "A fishing pole"
        },
        {
          "number": 36,
          "question": "Scout says in Chapter 6 that Mr. Avery boards a room across the street from whose house?",
          "options": [
            "Ruth Jones's",
            "Maxwell Green's",
            "Mrs. Dubose's",
            "Bob Ewell's"
          ],
          "answer": "Mrs. Dubose's"
        },
        {
          "number": 37,
          "question": "What does Jem tell Scout to not get tangled up with in the garden as the children steal into the Radley yard in Chapter 6?",
          "options": [
            "Blackberry vines",
            "Melon vines",
            "Collard greens",
            "Strawberry vines"
          ],
          "answer": "Collard greens"
        },
        {
          "number": 38,
          "question": "What does Jem get his pants caught on as the children run from the Radley yard in Chapter 6?",
          "options": [
            "A rake",
            "A tree branch",
            "A fence",
            "A bicycle"
          ],
          "answer": "A fence"
        },
        {
          "number": 39,
          "question": "What is the first name of the elder Mr. Radley?",
          "options": [
            "Nathan",
            "James",
            "Matthew",
            "Andrew"
          ],
          "answer": "Nathan"
        },
        {
          "number": 40,
          "question": "Scout says in Chapter 6 that \"Matches were dangerous, but\" what \"were fatal\"?",
          "options": [
            "Guns",
            "Cards",
            "Lighters",
            "Knives"
          ],
          "answer": "Cards"
        },
        {
          "number": 41,
          "question": "Dill tells Atticus that he won Jem's pants playing what game in Chapter 6?",
          "options": [
            "Strip poker",
            "Bridge",
            "Double-Dare",
            "Go Fish"
          ],
          "answer": "Strip poker"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "chapter_number": 7,
      "multiple_choice": [
        {
          "number": 42,
          "question": "At what time does Jem sneak out of the house to go get his pants in Chapter 6?",
          "options": [
            "12 a.m",
            "3 a.m",
            "4 a.m",
            "2 a.m"
          ],
          "answer": "2 a.m"
        },
        {
          "number": 43,
          "question": "What grade is Scout beginning in school in Chapter 7?",
          "options": [
            "Fourth grade",
            "First grade",
            "Third grade",
            "Second grade"
          ],
          "answer": "Second grade"
        },
        {
          "number": 44,
          "question": "What time does Scout get out of school each day in Chapter 7?",
          "options": [
            "2:00",
            "3:15",
            "2:30",
            "3:00"
          ],
          "answer": "3:00"
        },
        {
          "number": 45,
          "question": "What is the first object that Jem and Scout see in the knothole of the oak tree in Chapter 7?",
          "options": [
            "A watch",
            "A ball of twine",
            "A piece of gum",
            "A soap figurine"
          ],
          "answer": "A ball of twine"
        },
        {
          "number": 46,
          "question": "Jem tells Scout in Chapter 7 that it wasn't until he reached what grade that he learned anything of value in school?",
          "options": [
            "Fifth grade",
            "Third grade",
            "Sixth grade",
            "Fourth grade"
          ],
          "answer": "Sixth grade"
        },
        {
          "number": 47,
          "question": "The little figurines of a boy and girl that Scout and Jem find in the tree in Chapter 7 are carved from what material?",
          "options": [
            "Soap",
            "Clay",
            "Wood",
            "Stone"
          ],
          "answer": "Soap"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "chapter_number": 8,
      "multiple_choice": [
        {
          "number": 48,
          "question": "The medal that Scout and Jem find in the knothole of the oak tree in Chapter 7 is one that was awarded for what achievement?",
          "options": [
            "The Maycomb Spelling Bee",
            "Acts of Valor in WWI",
            "The Maycomb Sack Race",
            "The Maycomb Horse Race"
          ],
          "answer": "The Maycomb Spelling Bee"
        },
        {
          "number": 49,
          "question": "In the beginning of Chapter 8, Scout says that Maycomb County is experiencing the coldest winter since what year?",
          "options": [
            "1885",
            "1900",
            "1789",
            "1915"
          ],
          "answer": "1885"
        },
        {
          "number": 50,
          "question": "Scout claims in Chapter 8 that \"Mr. Avery said it was written on the Rosetta Stone that when children disobeyed their parents, smoked cigarettes and made war on each other,\" what would happen?",
          "options": [
            "The weather would change",
            "It would start raining",
            "It would get hot",
            "Someone would die"
          ],
          "answer": "The weather would change"
        },
        {
          "number": 51,
          "question": "What does Scout observe for the first time that makes her scream for Atticus saying that the world is ending in Chapter 8?",
          "options": [
            "Snow",
            "Rain",
            "Hail",
            "A tornado"
          ],
          "answer": "Snow"
        },
        {
          "number": 52,
          "question": "Who is the telephone operator that calls Atticus to tell him that school has been canceled in Chapter 8?",
          "options": [
            "Mayella Ewell",
            "Miss Maudie",
            "Miss Emily Davis's",
            "Eula May"
          ],
          "answer": "Eula May"
        },
        {
          "number": 53,
          "question": "At what time in the night does Atticus awaken Scout because of the fire on the block in Chapter 8?",
          "options": [
            "2:00 a.m",
            "12:00 a.m",
            "1:00 a.m",
            "3:00 a.m"
          ],
          "answer": "1:00 a.m"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "chapter_number": 9,
      "multiple_choice": [
        {
          "number": 54,
          "question": "Whose house has caught fire in Chapter 8?",
          "options": [
            "Miss Emily Davis's",
            "Miss Maudie's",
            "Mr. Underwood's",
            "Miss Stephanie Crawford's"
          ],
          "answer": "Miss Maudie's"
        },
        {
          "number": 55,
          "question": "Who does Scout almost come to blows with on the playground because he insults Atticus in the beginning of Chapter 9?",
          "options": [
            "Cecil Jacobs",
            "Bob Ewell",
            "John Taylor",
            "Dill"
          ],
          "answer": "Cecil Jacobs"
        },
        {
          "number": 56,
          "question": "Atticus tells Scout not to use the \"n\" word because it is what, in Chapter 9?",
          "options": [
            "Common",
            "Vulgar",
            "Obscene",
            "Lofty"
          ],
          "answer": "Common"
        },
        {
          "number": 57,
          "question": "What ailment does Scout try to get from Miss Rachel's cook's son by rubbing her head against his head in Chapter 9?",
          "options": [
            "The flu",
            "Mono",
            "Ringworm",
            "Asthma"
          ],
          "answer": "Ringworm"
        },
        {
          "number": 58,
          "question": "Who does Atticus say was kind enough to grant a postponement on the trial in Chapter 9?",
          "options": [
            "Cecil Jacobs",
            "Dill",
            "Bob Ewell",
            "John Taylor"
          ],
          "answer": "John Taylor"
        },
        {
          "number": 59,
          "question": "Who is described in Chapter 9 as \"Maycomb County’s sole surviving Confederate veteran\"?",
          "options": [
            "Bob Ewell",
            "Mr. Dolphus Raymond",
            "Mr. Tensaw Jones",
            "Ike Finch"
          ],
          "answer": "Ike Finch"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "chapter_number": 10,
      "multiple_choice": [
        {
          "number": 60,
          "question": "Of whom does Scout say in Chapter 9, \"I decided that she had been swapped at birth, that my grandparents had perhaps received a Crawford instead of a Finch\"?",
          "options": [
            "Aunt Elizabeth",
            "Aunt Clara",
            "Aunt Mayella",
            "Aunt Alexandra"
          ],
          "answer": "Aunt Alexandra"
        },
        {
          "number": 61,
          "question": "How old does Scout say Atticus is in Chapter 10?",
          "options": [
            "Nearly 40",
            "Nearly 60",
            "42",
            "Nearly 50"
          ],
          "answer": "Nearly 50"
        },
        {
          "number": 62,
          "question": "Who does Scout say taught her and Jem to shoot when they received air-rifles in Chapter 10?",
          "options": [
            "Mr. Dolphus Raymond",
            "Bob Ewell",
            "Uncle Jack",
            "Aunt Alexandra"
          ],
          "answer": "Uncle Jack"
        },
        {
          "number": 63,
          "question": "When Jem and Scout were given air-rifles, Atticus told Jem that it was a sin to kill a mockingbird, but that he could shoot all of what kind of bird that he wanted?",
          "options": [
            "Starlings",
            "Cardinals",
            "Bluejays",
            "Robins"
          ],
          "answer": "Bluejays"
        },
        {
          "number": 64,
          "question": "Why does Miss Maudie tell Scout it is a sin to kill a mockingbird?",
          "options": [
            "Because all they do is sing",
            "Because they are the color of heaven",
            "Because it is written in Leviticus",
            "Because they symbolize peace"
          ],
          "answer": "Because all they do is sing"
        },
        {
          "number": 65,
          "question": "What game does Miss Maudie say Atticus is the best at in town in Chapter 10?",
          "options": [
            "Checkers",
            "Chess",
            "Poker",
            "Basketball"
          ],
          "answer": "Checkers"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "chapter_number": 11,
      "multiple_choice": [
        {
          "number": 66,
          "question": "What kind of sport are the Methodists and the Baptists playing as a benefit in Chapter 10?",
          "options": [
            "Volleyball",
            "Touch football",
            "Softball",
            "Basketball"
          ],
          "answer": "Touch football"
        },
        {
          "number": 67,
          "question": "What does Jem intend to buy for himself with his birthday money in the beginning of Chapter 11?",
          "options": [
            "A miniature steam engine",
            "A pocket watch",
            "A bicycle",
            "A skateboard"
          ],
          "answer": "A miniature steam engine"
        },
        {
          "number": 68,
          "question": "The twirling baton that Scout longs for in Chapter 11 is sold at what store in town?",
          "options": [
            "Sears",
            "V. J. Elmore's",
            "J. C. Penney's",
            "Wal-Mart"
          ],
          "answer": "V. J. Elmore's"
        },
        {
          "number": 69,
          "question": "How much does the twirling baton cost that Scout longs for in Chapter 11?",
          "options": [
            "2 dollars",
            "1 dollar",
            "50 cents",
            "17 cents"
          ],
          "answer": "17 cents"
        },
        {
          "number": 70,
          "question": "What \"dim organization on the north side of the square\" does Mrs. Dubose tell Scout she'll grow up to work at in Chapter 11?",
          "options": [
            "The White Horse",
            "The O.K. Cafe",
            "The Lost Coast",
            "Jenny's Cafe"
          ],
          "answer": "The O.K. Cafe"
        },
        {
          "number": 71,
          "question": "What does Jem do after Mrs. Dubose says derogatory things about Atticus and enrages him in Chapter 11?",
          "options": [
            "He calls the police",
            "He shoots her dog",
            "He destroys her camelias",
            "He breaks her window"
          ],
          "answer": "He destroys her camelias"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "chapter_number": 12,
      "multiple_choice": [
        {
          "number": 72,
          "question": "What is the name of the black man that Atticus Finch is assigned to defend in the novel?",
          "options": [
            "Bob Ewell",
            "Mr. Dolphus Raymond",
            "Tom Robinson",
            "Cecil Jacobs"
          ],
          "answer": "Tom Robinson"
        },
        {
          "number": 73,
          "question": "How old is Jem in the beginning of Chapter 12?",
          "options": [
            "12",
            "15",
            "13",
            "11"
          ],
          "answer": "12"
        },
        {
          "number": 74,
          "question": "What does Scout ask Atticus if Jem might have when Jem's appetite grows considerably in Chapter 12?",
          "options": [
            "A tapeworm",
            "The measles",
            "Meningitis",
            "Pneumonia"
          ],
          "answer": "A tapeworm"
        },
        {
          "number": 75,
          "question": "What profession does Dill say his new father has in his letter in Chapter 12?",
          "options": [
            "Doctor",
            "Professor",
            "Musician",
            "Lawyer"
          ],
          "answer": "Lawyer"
        },
        {
          "number": 76,
          "question": "For how long does Atticus leave home because the legislature is called into emergency session in Chapter 12?",
          "options": [
            "3 weeks",
            "1 week",
            "2 weeks",
            "2 months"
          ],
          "answer": "2 weeks"
        },
        {
          "number": 77,
          "question": "What is the name of Calpurnia's church that she takes Scout and Jem to in Chapter 12?",
          "options": [
            "First Purchase African M.E. Church",
            "The Second Street Baptist Church",
            "St. Edwards' Catholic Church",
            "The First Methodist Church"
          ],
          "answer": "First Purchase African M.E. Church"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "chapter_number": 13,
      "multiple_choice": [
        {
          "number": 78,
          "question": "What is the name of the Maycomb trash collector that Jem and Scout see at church in Chapter 12?",
          "options": [
            "Jeb",
            "James",
            "Zeebo",
            "Dill"
          ],
          "answer": "Zeebo"
        },
        {
          "number": 79,
          "question": "On what day of the week does Aunt Alexandra arrive at the Finch household in Chapter 13?",
          "options": [
            "Friday",
            "Sunday",
            "Saturday",
            "Tuesday"
          ],
          "answer": "Sunday"
        },
        {
          "number": 80,
          "question": "Where is Atticus returning from in the beginning of Chapter 13?",
          "options": [
            "New Orleans, Louisiana",
            "Montgomery, Alabama",
            "Washington, D.C",
            "Houston, Texas"
          ],
          "answer": "Montgomery, Alabama"
        },
        {
          "number": 81,
          "question": "How far is Maycomb from Finch's Landing?",
          "options": [
            "20 miles",
            "30 miles",
            "40 miles",
            "10 miles"
          ],
          "answer": "20 miles"
        },
        {
          "number": 82,
          "question": "What word is used in the novel to refer to homemade liquor?",
          "options": [
            "Moonbeam",
            "Shinny",
            "Ginny",
            "Shiner"
          ],
          "answer": "Shinny"
        },
        {
          "number": 83,
          "question": "Aunt Alexandra presents a book to Jem and Scout that was written by what cousin of theirs in Chapter 13?",
          "options": [
            "Mr. Tensaw Jones",
            "Joshua St. Clair",
            "John Taylor",
            "Cecil Jacobs"
          ],
          "answer": "Joshua St. Clair"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "chapter_number": 14,
      "multiple_choice": [
        {
          "number": 84,
          "question": "Atticus asks Jem and Scout as he leaves their room in Chapter 13, \"Do you think I'll end up costing the family\" how much money?",
          "options": [
            "$200",
            "$5,000",
            "$500",
            "$10,000"
          ],
          "answer": "$500"
        },
        {
          "number": 85,
          "question": "What does Scout think is under her bed when she goes to get Jem in Chapter 14?",
          "options": [
            "A cat",
            "A bird",
            "A rat",
            "A snake"
          ],
          "answer": "A snake"
        },
        {
          "number": 86,
          "question": "How much money does Dill say he took from his mother's purse in order to come to Maycomb in Chapter 14?",
          "options": [
            "$50",
            "$13",
            "$23",
            "$5"
          ],
          "answer": "$13"
        },
        {
          "number": 87,
          "question": "How many miles away from home has Dill traveled to come to Maycomb in Chapter 14?",
          "options": [
            "150",
            "300",
            "50",
            "200"
          ],
          "answer": "300"
        },
        {
          "number": 88,
          "question": "Who does Jem go to tell that Dill has arrived at the Finch household in Chapter 14?",
          "options": [
            "Calpurnia",
            "Miss Rachel",
            "Atticus",
            "Aunt Alexandra"
          ],
          "answer": "Atticus"
        },
        {
          "number": 89,
          "question": "What word does Atticus define for Scout in Chapter 14 as \"carnal knowledge of a female by force and without consent\"?",
          "options": [
            "Rape",
            "Insolence",
            "Fortitude",
            "Coercion"
          ],
          "answer": "Rape"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "chapter_number": 15,
      "multiple_choice": [
        {
          "number": 90,
          "question": "What is Dill's response when Scout asks him in Chapter 14, “Why do you reckon Boo Radley’s never run off?”",
          "options": [
            "\"He's shackled to a wall, so he can't.\"",
            "\"He isn't smart enough to think of it.\"",
            "“Maybe he doesn’t have anywhere to run off to",
            "\"He's probably tried a dozen times.\""
          ],
          "answer": "“Maybe he doesn’t have anywhere to run off to"
        },
        {
          "number": 91,
          "question": "What is the name of the Sheriff of Maycomb County?",
          "options": [
            "Bob Ewell",
            "Dolphus Raymond",
            "Tensaw Jones",
            "Heck Tate"
          ],
          "answer": "Heck Tate"
        },
        {
          "number": 92,
          "question": "Who does Atticus say shamed the Ku Klux Klan away from Maycomb when they paraded around his house once in Chapter 15?",
          "options": [
            "John Taylor",
            "Maxwell Green",
            "Cecil Jacobs",
            "Sam Levy"
          ],
          "answer": "Sam Levy"
        },
        {
          "number": 93,
          "question": "Who is the sole owner, editor and printer of The Maycomb Tribune?",
          "options": [
            "John Taylor",
            "Cecil Jacobs",
            "Sam Levy",
            "Mr. Underwood"
          ],
          "answer": "Mr. Underwood"
        },
        {
          "number": 94,
          "question": "What kind of car does Atticus Finch own and keep in the garage?",
          "options": [
            "A Ford",
            "A Subaru",
            "A Rolls-Royce",
            "A Chevrolet"
          ],
          "answer": "A Chevrolet"
        },
        {
          "number": 95,
          "question": "Who does Scout tell Mr. Cunningham to say hello to for her in Chapter 15?",
          "options": [
            "Jasper",
            "Pete",
            "Cletus",
            "Walter"
          ],
          "answer": "Walter"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "chapter_number": 16,
      "multiple_choice": [
        {
          "number": 96,
          "question": "Who speaks from the shadows and is revealed to be holding a double-barrel shotgun with the intention of protecting Atticus in Chapter 15?",
          "options": [
            "Sam Levy",
            "Cecil Jacobs",
            "John Taylor",
            "Mr. Underwood"
          ],
          "answer": "Mr. Underwood"
        },
        {
          "number": 97,
          "question": "What does Jem eat for breakfast in the beginning of Chapter 16?",
          "options": [
            "Four pancakes",
            "Six muffins",
            "Cereal",
            "Three eggs"
          ],
          "answer": "Three eggs"
        },
        {
          "number": 98,
          "question": "Scouts says in Chapter 16, \"Atticus said naming people after Confederate generals made\" what?",
          "options": [
            "Future jailbirds",
            "Angry children",
            "Slow, steady drinkers",
            "Wife beaters"
          ],
          "answer": "Slow, steady drinkers"
        },
        {
          "number": 99,
          "question": "What towns-person is described by Jem in Chapter 16 as voting \"the straight Prohibition ticket\"?",
          "options": [
            "John Taylor",
            "Mr. Tensaw Jones",
            "Maxwell Green",
            "Sam Levy"
          ],
          "answer": "Mr. Tensaw Jones"
        },
        {
          "number": 100,
          "question": "What lady from Maycomb is described in Chapter 16 as one who dips snuff in private?",
          "options": [
            "Miss Emily Davis",
            "Miss Stephanie Crawford",
            "Mayella Ewell",
            "Ruth Jones"
          ],
          "answer": "Miss Emily Davis"
        },
        {
          "number": 101,
          "question": "What kind of cola does Scout describe the black attendees of the trial drinking in Chapter 16?",
          "options": [
            "Coca Cola",
            "Nehi Cola",
            "Pepsi Cola",
            "Dr. Pepper"
          ],
          "answer": "Nehi Cola"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "chapter_number": 17,
      "multiple_choice": [
        {
          "number": 102,
          "question": "Of whom does Jem say in Chapter 16, \"Lives by himself way down near the county line. He’s got a colored woman and all sorts of mixed chillun\"?",
          "options": [
            "Mr. Dolphus Raymond",
            "Bob Ewell",
            "Mr. Tensaw Jones",
            "Cecil Jacobs"
          ],
          "answer": "Mr. Dolphus Raymond"
        },
        {
          "number": 103,
          "question": "Where is Mr. Gilmer said to be from in Chapter 17?",
          "options": [
            "Little Rock",
            "Abbottsville",
            "Ashland",
            "Mobile"
          ],
          "answer": "Abbottsville"
        },
        {
          "number": 104,
          "question": "Who does the Sheriff say called him to the Ewell residence on the night of the alleged crime in Chapter 17?",
          "options": [
            "Tom Robinson",
            "Mr. Dolphus Raymond",
            "Bob Ewell",
            "Mayella Ewell"
          ],
          "answer": "Bob Ewell"
        },
        {
          "number": 105,
          "question": "On what date was the Sheriff contacted to go to the Ewell residence, according to his testimony in Chapter 17?",
          "options": [
            "November 21",
            "July 7",
            "June 13",
            "September 12"
          ],
          "answer": "November 21"
        },
        {
          "number": 106,
          "question": "Who is Dill sitting next to in the courtroom in Chapter 17?",
          "options": [
            "Cecil Jacobs",
            "Reverend Sykes",
            "Miss Stephanie Crawford",
            "Mr. Dolphus Raymond"
          ],
          "answer": "Reverend Sykes"
        },
        {
          "number": 107,
          "question": "What is the name of the young woman who claims to have been raped by Tom Robinson in the trial?",
          "options": [
            "Miss Maudie",
            "Mayella Ewell",
            "Stephanie Crawford",
            "Ruth Jones"
          ],
          "answer": "Mayella Ewell"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "chapter_number": 18,
      "multiple_choice": [
        {
          "number": 108,
          "question": "What is noted by Atticus when he has Bob Ewell write his name before the court in Chapter 17?",
          "options": [
            "Ewell is illiterate",
            "Ewell is left-handed",
            "Ewell is right-handed",
            "Ewell is blind"
          ],
          "answer": "Ewell is left-handed"
        },
        {
          "number": 109,
          "question": "What is Mayella Ewell's middle name?",
          "options": [
            "Leigh",
            "Violet",
            "Jasmine",
            "Ellen"
          ],
          "answer": "Violet"
        },
        {
          "number": 110,
          "question": "How old does Mayella Ewell says she is when she takes the stand in Chapter 18?",
          "options": [
            "17",
            "16",
            "19",
            "22"
          ],
          "answer": "19"
        },
        {
          "number": 111,
          "question": "How much money does Mayella say she offered to Tom Robinson to bust up a chiffarobe for her in Chapter 18?",
          "options": [
            "A dime",
            "A penny",
            "A quarter",
            "A nickel"
          ],
          "answer": "A nickel"
        },
        {
          "number": 112,
          "question": "How many siblings does Mayella Ewell have?",
          "options": [
            "6",
            "7",
            "3",
            "5"
          ],
          "answer": "7"
        },
        {
          "number": 113,
          "question": "How did Tom Robinson injure his left arm, according to Reverend Sykes in Chapter 18?",
          "options": [
            "It was caught in a well",
            "It was amputated in a car accident",
            "It was caught in a cotton gin",
            "It was injured during a shooting"
          ],
          "answer": "It was caught in a cotton gin"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "chapter_number": 19,
      "multiple_choice": [
        {
          "number": 114,
          "question": "How many witnesses does Atticus say he has for the court in the end of Chapter 18?",
          "options": [
            "Four",
            "Three",
            "Two",
            "One"
          ],
          "answer": "One"
        },
        {
          "number": 115,
          "question": "Who is the judge that oversees the trial of Tom Robinson?",
          "options": [
            "Judge Taylor",
            "Judge Tate",
            "Judge Dixon",
            "Judge Murphy"
          ],
          "answer": "Judge Taylor"
        },
        {
          "number": 116,
          "question": "How old is Tom Robinson when he takes the stand in Chapter 19?",
          "options": [
            "29",
            "32",
            "22",
            "25"
          ],
          "answer": "25"
        },
        {
          "number": 117,
          "question": "How many children does Tom Robinson say he has in Chapter 19?",
          "options": [
            "3",
            "4",
            "2",
            "5"
          ],
          "answer": "3"
        },
        {
          "number": 118,
          "question": "According to Tom Robinson's testimony, he spent thirty days in jail once before when he was convicted of what crime?",
          "options": [
            "Animal cruelty",
            "Domestic abuse",
            "Disorderly conduct",
            "Vandalism"
          ],
          "answer": "Disorderly conduct"
        },
        {
          "number": 119,
          "question": "For whom does Tom Robinson say he worked at the time of the crime in Chapter 19?",
          "options": [
            "Mr. Tensaw Jones",
            "Mr. Link Deas",
            "Miss Stephanie Crawford",
            "Mr. Dolphus Raymond"
          ],
          "answer": "Mr. Link Deas"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "chapter_number": 20,
      "multiple_choice": [
        {
          "number": 120,
          "question": "What reason does Tom Robinson give for why he helped out Mayella Ewell periodically in Chapter 19?",
          "options": [
            "He needed money",
            "He felt sorry for her",
            "He hoped she'd marry him",
            "He was attracted to her"
          ],
          "answer": "He felt sorry for her"
        },
        {
          "number": 121,
          "question": "Who does Mr. Dolphus Raymond offer a drink to in the beginning of Chapter 20?",
          "options": [
            "Jem",
            "Dill",
            "Scout",
            "Calpurnia"
          ],
          "answer": "Dill"
        },
        {
          "number": 122,
          "question": "The children discover that Mr. Dolphus Raymond is actually drinking what from his brown paper bag in Chapter 20?",
          "options": [
            "Coca Cola",
            "Dr. Pepper",
            "Whiskey",
            "Beer"
          ],
          "answer": "Coca Cola"
        },
        {
          "number": 123,
          "question": "What \"offense\" does Atticus say Mayella Ewell committed and then attempted to cover her guilt for in his final statement to the jury?",
          "options": [
            "She was secretly married",
            "She fell down a well",
            "She killed her mother",
            "She tempted a black man"
          ],
          "answer": "She tempted a black man"
        },
        {
          "number": 124,
          "question": "Whom does Atticus Finch insinuate actually beat up Mayella Ewell in his closing statements to the jury?",
          "options": [
            "Tom Robinson",
            "Mr. Link Deas",
            "Bob Ewell",
            "Mr. Tensaw Jones"
          ],
          "answer": "Bob Ewell"
        },
        {
          "number": 125,
          "question": "What year does Atticus Finch say it is in his closing statements in Chapter 20?",
          "options": [
            "1931",
            "1926",
            "1941",
            "1935"
          ],
          "answer": "1935"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "chapter_number": 21,
      "multiple_choice": [
        {
          "number": 126,
          "question": "What does Atticus Finch claim are the \"great levelers\" and the place in this country where \"all men are created equal\" in Chapter 20?",
          "options": [
            "The factory floors",
            "The jails",
            "The courts",
            "The senate rooms"
          ],
          "answer": "The courts"
        },
        {
          "number": 127,
          "question": "When Atticus opens the envelope that Calpurnia brings him at the courtroom in Chapter 21, he tells the judge that the letter is from whom?",
          "options": [
            "Aunt Alexandra",
            "Tom Robinson",
            "Dill Harris",
            "Uncle Jack"
          ],
          "answer": "Aunt Alexandra"
        },
        {
          "number": 128,
          "question": "Who points out the children sitting in the balcony of the courtroom to Atticus in Chapter 21?",
          "options": [
            "Mr. Underwood",
            "Mr. Tensaw Jones",
            "Maxwell Green",
            "Dolphus Raymond"
          ],
          "answer": "Mr. Underwood"
        },
        {
          "number": 129,
          "question": "How long has the jury been out when Jem, Scout, and Dill return from eating lunch in Chapter 21?",
          "options": [
            "2 hours",
            "10 minutes",
            "1 hour",
            "30 minutes"
          ],
          "answer": "30 minutes"
        },
        {
          "number": 130,
          "question": "What is the name of the court reporter who chain smokes in Chapter 21?",
          "options": [
            "Bill",
            "Bert",
            "Jerry",
            "Mitch"
          ],
          "answer": "Bert"
        },
        {
          "number": 131,
          "question": "What is the verdict in the Tom Robinson trial in Chapter 21?",
          "options": [
            "Guilty",
            "Innocent by reason of insanity",
            "Innocent",
            "There is a hung jury"
          ],
          "answer": "Guilty"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "chapter_number": 22,
      "multiple_choice": [
        {
          "number": 132,
          "question": "What do the black attendees of the trial do as Atticus Finch exits the courthouse in Chapter 21?",
          "options": [
            "They stand",
            "They riot",
            "They hiss at him",
            "They wave"
          ],
          "answer": "They stand"
        },
        {
          "number": 133,
          "question": "What newspaper is Atticus reading when Scout and Jem awaken in Chapter 22?",
          "options": [
            "The Mobile Register",
            "The New York Times",
            "The Houston Chronicle",
            "The Chicago Tribune"
          ],
          "answer": "The Mobile Register"
        },
        {
          "number": 134,
          "question": "What food item does Calpurnia say Tom Robinson's father sent over to the Finch's in Chapter 22?",
          "options": [
            "A dozen eggs",
            "A chicken",
            "Pig's feet",
            "Bread pudding"
          ],
          "answer": "A chicken"
        },
        {
          "number": 135,
          "question": "What dessert does Miss Maudie offer to Jem and the other children in Chapter 22?",
          "options": [
            "Ice cream",
            "Pralines",
            "Pie",
            "Cake"
          ],
          "answer": "Cake"
        },
        {
          "number": 136,
          "question": "According to the narrator in Chapter 22, \"Court-appointed defenses were usually given to\" what latest addition to the bar?",
          "options": [
            "Link Deas",
            "Dolphus Raymond",
            "Bob Ewell",
            "Maxwell Green"
          ],
          "answer": "Maxwell Green"
        },
        {
          "number": 137,
          "question": "What does Dill say he's going to be when he grows up as Miss Rachel approaches them on the sidewalk in Chapter 22?",
          "options": [
            "A doctor",
            "A policeman",
            "A clown",
            "A lawyer"
          ],
          "answer": "A clown"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "chapter_number": 23,
      "multiple_choice": [
        {
          "number": 138,
          "question": "Who is said to have spit in Atticus's face and threatened him in Chapter 22?",
          "options": [
            "Bob Ewell",
            "Dolphus Raymond",
            "Maxwell Green",
            "Link Deas"
          ],
          "answer": "Bob Ewell"
        },
        {
          "number": 139,
          "question": "What store does Miss Stephanie Crawford say she was leaving when she saw Atticus get threatened in Chapter 23?",
          "options": [
            "Sears",
            "Jitney Jungle",
            "Wal-Mart",
            "J.C. Penney's"
          ],
          "answer": "Jitney Jungle"
        },
        {
          "number": 140,
          "question": "Jem says in Chapter 23 of Atticus, \"He told me havin' a gun around's an invitation\" for what?",
          "options": [
            "Somebody to rob you",
            "Somebody to stab you",
            "Somebody to shoot you",
            "Accidents"
          ],
          "answer": "Somebody to shoot you"
        },
        {
          "number": 141,
          "question": "Where is Enfield Prison Farm said to be in Chapter 23?",
          "options": [
            "Clark County",
            "Chester County",
            "Jackson County",
            "Warren County"
          ],
          "answer": "Chester County"
        },
        {
          "number": 142,
          "question": "What will happen to Tom Robinson if he loses his appeal, according to Atticus in Chapter 23?",
          "options": [
            "He'll be placed on parole",
            "He'll spend life in prison",
            "He'll spend 20 years in prison",
            "He'll receive the death penalty"
          ],
          "answer": "He'll receive the death penalty"
        },
        {
          "number": 143,
          "question": "What does Jem believe the justice system should get rid of in Chapter 23?",
          "options": [
            "Verdicts",
            "Lawyers",
            "Judges",
            "Juries"
          ],
          "answer": "Juries"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "chapter_number": 24,
      "multiple_choice": [
        {
          "number": 144,
          "question": "Jem and Scout learn in Chapter 23 that the one juror that wanted to find Tom Robinson innocent was a relative of what family?",
          "options": [
            "The Cunninghams",
            "The Finches",
            "The Stewarts",
            "The Ewells"
          ],
          "answer": "The Cunninghams"
        },
        {
          "number": 145,
          "question": "Where have Jem and Dill gone in the beginning of Chapter 24?",
          "options": [
            "The Colorado River",
            "Barker's Eddy",
            "Arkansas",
            "Montgomery"
          ],
          "answer": "Barker's Eddy"
        },
        {
          "number": 146,
          "question": "What month is it in the beginning of Chapter 24?",
          "options": [
            "June",
            "July",
            "March",
            "August"
          ],
          "answer": "August"
        },
        {
          "number": 147,
          "question": "What does Scout say \"always filled me with vague apprehension and a firm desire to be elsewhere\" in Chapter 24?",
          "options": [
            "Groups of ladies",
            "Snakes",
            "Little kids",
            "Schoolteachers"
          ],
          "answer": "Groups of ladies"
        },
        {
          "number": 148,
          "question": "What word used in Chapter 24 refers to a person who pretends to have virtues, moral or religious beliefs, principles, etc., that he or she does not actually possess?",
          "options": [
            "Suffragette",
            "Wanderer",
            "Abolitionist",
            "Hypocrite"
          ],
          "answer": "Hypocrite"
        },
        {
          "number": 149,
          "question": "What is the name of Tom Robinson's wife?",
          "options": [
            "Helen",
            "Carol",
            "Anne",
            "Sarah"
          ],
          "answer": "Helen"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "chapter_number": 25,
      "multiple_choice": [
        {
          "number": 150,
          "question": "How many bullet holes does Atticus say they found on Tom Robinson in Chapter 24?",
          "options": [
            "12",
            "6",
            "22",
            "17"
          ],
          "answer": "17"
        },
        {
          "number": 151,
          "question": "What bug is Scout about to kill in the beginning of Chapter 25 when Jem tells her to take it outside?",
          "options": [
            "A wolf spider",
            "A cockroach",
            "A lighting bug",
            "A roly-poly"
          ],
          "answer": "A roly-poly"
        },
        {
          "number": 152,
          "question": "Jem and Dill had been heading home from where when they'd encountered Atticus going to the Robinson home, according to Scout in Chapter 25?",
          "options": [
            "Montgomery",
            "Barker's Eddy",
            "Church",
            "Sears"
          ],
          "answer": "Barker's Eddy"
        },
        {
          "number": 153,
          "question": "What does Dill say the children were playing in front of Tom Robinson's residence when Atticus arrived in Chapter 25?",
          "options": [
            "Marbles",
            "Poker",
            "Football",
            "Basketball"
          ],
          "answer": "Marbles"
        },
        {
          "number": 154,
          "question": "Who writes a scathing editorial in the newspaper about the Tom Robinson ordeal in Chapter 25?",
          "options": [
            "Emily Davis",
            "Link Deas",
            "Dolphus Raymond",
            "Mr. Underwood"
          ],
          "answer": "Mr. Underwood"
        },
        {
          "number": 155,
          "question": "Who \"told Aunt Alexandra in Jem’s presence (“Oh foot, he’s old enough to listen.”) that Mr. Ewell said it made one down and about two more to go\" in Chapter 25?",
          "options": [
            "Miss Stephanie Crawford",
            "Ruth Jones",
            "Emily Davis",
            "Mayella Ewell"
          ],
          "answer": "Miss Stephanie Crawford"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "chapter_number": 26,
      "multiple_choice": [
        {
          "number": 156,
          "question": "What word from Chapter 25 refers to generous actions or donations to aid the poor, ill, or helpless?",
          "options": [
            "Coronation",
            "Charity",
            "Cultivation",
            "Absolution"
          ],
          "answer": "Charity"
        },
        {
          "number": 157,
          "question": "What grade in school has Scout begun in the beginning of Chapter 26?",
          "options": [
            "Fourth grade",
            "Fifth grade",
            "Third grade",
            "Sixth grade"
          ],
          "answer": "Third grade"
        },
        {
          "number": 158,
          "question": "Jem is in what grade in school in the beginning of Chapter 26?",
          "options": [
            "Fifth grade",
            "Seventh grade",
            "Fourth grade",
            "Sixth grade"
          ],
          "answer": "Seventh grade"
        },
        {
          "number": 159,
          "question": "Who does Cecil Jacobs describe in Chapter 26 as having \"been after the Jews and he’s puttin‘ ’em in prisons and he’s taking away all their property and he won’t let any of ‘em out of the country\"?",
          "options": [
            "Adolf Hitler",
            "Benito Mussolini",
            "Saddam Hussein",
            "Benedict Arnold"
          ],
          "answer": "Adolf Hitler"
        },
        {
          "number": 160,
          "question": "What quotation does Scout cite in Chapter 26 when her teacher asks for the definition of Democracy?",
          "options": [
            "“‘Equal rights for all, special privileges for none.’\"",
            "\"Practicing the same definition of 'fair' to everyone, regardless of color, gender, or age.\"",
            "\"Elected individuals to represent an entire community.\"",
            "\"Being fair, even when you don't want to be.\""
          ],
          "answer": "“‘Equal rights for all, special privileges for none.’\""
        },
        {
          "number": 161,
          "question": "What kind of government does Miss Gates say Germany operates under in Chapter 26?",
          "options": [
            "A monarchy",
            "A confederacy",
            "A democracy",
            "A dictatorship"
          ],
          "answer": "A dictatorship"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "chapter_number": 27,
      "multiple_choice": [
        {
          "number": 162,
          "question": "What study does Scout say she's never been a fan of in Chapter 26?",
          "options": [
            "History",
            "Arithmetic",
            "Literature",
            "Science"
          ],
          "answer": "Arithmetic"
        },
        {
          "number": 163,
          "question": "Scout says in Chapter 27 that Bob Ewell is the \"only man I ever heard of who was fired from the WPA for\" what?",
          "options": [
            "Drinking",
            "Domestic abuse",
            "Cancer",
            "Laziness"
          ],
          "answer": "Laziness"
        },
        {
          "number": 164,
          "question": "Who does Scout refer to as the \"Welfare lady\" in Chapter 27?",
          "options": [
            "Ruth Jones",
            "Mayella Ewell",
            "Miss Maudie",
            "Emily Davis"
          ],
          "answer": "Ruth Jones"
        },
        {
          "number": 165,
          "question": "Who has gone out of his way to make a job for Helen Robinson in Chapter 27?",
          "options": [
            "Miss Maudie",
            "Miss Stephanie Crawford",
            "Mr. Dolphus Raymond",
            "Mr. Link Deas"
          ],
          "answer": "Mr. Link Deas"
        },
        {
          "number": 166,
          "question": "What does \"NRA\" refer to in the novel?",
          "options": [
            "National Retaliatory Act",
            "National Refurbishment Act",
            "National Recovery Act",
            "National Rifle Association"
          ],
          "answer": "National Recovery Act"
        },
        {
          "number": 167,
          "question": "Of Misses Tutti and Frutti Barber, Scout says in Chapter 27 that they \"were rumored to be Republicans, having migrated from Clanton, Alabama\" in what year?",
          "options": [
            "1885",
            "1856",
            "1901",
            "1911"
          ],
          "answer": "1911"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "chapter_number": 28,
      "multiple_choice": [
        {
          "number": 168,
          "question": "What are the first names of Misses Tutti and Frutti?",
          "options": [
            "Sarah and Frances",
            "June and Mary",
            "Anne and Alva",
            "Wilma and Betty"
          ],
          "answer": "Sarah and Frances"
        },
        {
          "number": 169,
          "question": "What does Scout dress up as for the Halloween parade in Chapter 28?",
          "options": [
            "A mouse",
            "A cat",
            "A werewolf",
            "A ham"
          ],
          "answer": "A ham"
        },
        {
          "number": 170,
          "question": "Scout describes the lament of the bluejay in Chapter 28 as a repetitive sounding of what phrase?",
          "options": [
            "Why Me?",
            "Too Bad",
            "Poor Will",
            "Oh No"
          ],
          "answer": "Poor Will"
        },
        {
          "number": 171,
          "question": "How much money does Jem give to Scout to spend at the Halloween pageant in Chapter 28?",
          "options": [
            "2 dollars",
            "1 dollar",
            "10 cents",
            "30 cents"
          ],
          "answer": "30 cents"
        },
        {
          "number": 172,
          "question": "Who does Jem leave Scout to hang out with at the Halloween pageant in Chapter 28?",
          "options": [
            "John Taylor",
            "Stephanie Crawford",
            "Link Deas",
            "Cecil Jacobs"
          ],
          "answer": "Cecil Jacobs"
        },
        {
          "number": 173,
          "question": "What is the language of the Creek Indians?",
          "options": [
            "Inuit",
            "Bengali",
            "Cherokee",
            "Mvskoke"
          ],
          "answer": "Mvskoke"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "chapter_number": 29,
      "multiple_choice": [
        {
          "number": 174,
          "question": "Who is killed in Chapter 28?",
          "options": [
            "Scout Finch",
            "Boo Radley",
            "Bob Ewell",
            "Jem Finch"
          ],
          "answer": "Bob Ewell"
        },
        {
          "number": 175,
          "question": "What does Sheriff Tate say he believes saved Scout's life in Chapter 29?",
          "options": [
            "Her shoes",
            "Her wits",
            "Her uncle",
            "Her costume"
          ],
          "answer": "Her costume"
        },
        {
          "number": 176,
          "question": "How has Jem been injured in Chapter 29?",
          "options": [
            "His ribs are broken",
            "His collar bone is broken",
            "His arm is broken",
            "His leg is broken"
          ],
          "answer": "His arm is broken"
        },
        {
          "number": 177,
          "question": "Who does Scout point out as the person that saved her and Jem from their attacker in Chapter 29?",
          "options": [
            "John Taylor",
            "Cecil Jacobs",
            "Sam Levy",
            "Boo Radley"
          ],
          "answer": "Boo Radley"
        },
        {
          "number": 178,
          "question": "Who is the doctor that has been called to see to Jem in Chapter 30?",
          "options": [
            "Dr. Reynolds",
            "Dr. Anderson",
            "Dr. Caffrey",
            "Dr. Smith"
          ],
          "answer": "Dr. Reynolds"
        },
        {
          "number": 179,
          "question": "How does the Sheriff contend that Mr. Ewell died in Chapter 30?",
          "options": [
            "He fell on his knife",
            "He was stabbed by Boo Radley",
            "He was shot by Scout Finch",
            "He was stabbed by Jem Finch"
          ],
          "answer": "He fell on his knife"
        },
        {
          "number": 180,
          "question": "What flowers does Miss Maudie grow and obsess over in the novel?",
          "options": [
            "Azaleas",
            "Pansies",
            "Orchids",
            "Roses"
          ],
          "answer": "Azaleas"
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}